mvrck.mobi 2017-11-12

# MVRCK

This Privacy Policy was last modified on March 1st, 2015 and is effective as of April 1st, 2015. 

This is our official Privacy Policy which forms part of your legal agreement with us UNDER OUR TERMS OF USE. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post the effective date of any change at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your use of our Digital Property after the effective date of any such modification means you accept and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. We urge you to come back to this digital page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you. 

COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION 

"Personal Information" may include information such as your name, postal address, email, and telephone number. You voluntarily provide this information to us, for example, when you register with our Digital Property or make a request for information or services. We may use this information for purposes including responding to your requests as well as to provide you access to interactive features (i.e., conferences or webinars). 

COLLECTING NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We will use the term "cookie" to refer generically to any technology that can collect or transmit information about visits to our Digital Properties. "Cookie" information typically includes such data as the referral web domain, the type of operating system and browser you are using, mobile device identifiers, the date and time of your visit, location data, information relating to activities on our Digital Properties (e.g., "clickstream" data) and other technical attributes of visits to our Digital Properties. We use the information collected through cookies to analyze trends, administer our Websites, track movements on our Website or applications Digital Properties and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so we can continually improve our Digital Properties.   
We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. One of the products we use to do this on our own platform. 

HOW WE USE INFORMATION   
We will use information we collect or obtain when you use our Digital Properties as described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time of collection, to: 

Conduct internal research;   
Operate and administer our Digital Properties;   
Ensure compliance with our Terms of Use;   
Respond to your requests for products, services, and/or information;   
Communicate with you about MAVERICK products, services, events, promotions, and other items we believe will be of interest to you;   
Fulfill your purchases or registrations; and   
Provide member services including publishing a directory for members. 

ADVERTISERS 

In the course of serving advertisements to our Website, our operational service provider may use cookies and other technologies. 

INFORMATION SHARING 

We may share Personal Information with our operational service providers to assist us in connection with our Digital Properties, or other services we provide. 

SECURITY 

As you may appreciate, the Internet is a public network and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and MAVERICK or others to, through, or from our Digital Property, will be free from unauthorized access or interference by third parties. By using our Digital Property, you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability that may arise. We have put in place reasonable procedures to help safeguard information and we limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees who need access in order to perform their duties. 

CONTACT US 

For questions relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: privacy@mvrck.mobi or +54 11 4775 7010 or by mail, proper postage prepaid, at MVRCK S.A., LIMA 355, 3°A, BUENOS AIRES, 1073, ARGENTINA, Attention: Privacy Administrator
